const guess = [
  {"question":"What are the healthiest teas?",
   "answer":"Honesty, Integrity and Loyalty" 
  },
  {"question":"What are the strongest days of the week?",
  "answer":"Saturday and Sunday, the rest are weekdays " 
  },
  {"question":"What did one cell say to his sister cell that stepped on his toe?",
  "answer":"Mitosis!" 
  },
  {"question":"What ado you call a snobbish criminal going down the stairs?",
  "answer":"A condescending con descending" 
  },
  {"question":"What do you call a bunch of chess players bragging about their games in a hotel lobby?",
  "answer":"Chess nuts boasting in an open foyer" 
  },
  {"question":"Where did Noah keep his bees?",
  "answer":"In the Ark Hives" 
  },
  {"question":"What do you call the security guards outside the Samsung store?",
  "answer":"The Guardians of the Galaxy" 
  },
  {"question":"Why should you NEVER use the bathroom when you are around Pokemon?",
  "answer":"They might Pikachu" 
  },
  {"question":"What Do You Call Something That Is Shorter Than Most Mums?",
  "answer":"The minimum" 
  },
  {"question":"What Do You Call Something That Is Shorter Than Most Mums?",
  "answer":"The minimum" 
  }

]
export {guess}